Let's drill our Egyptian walk switching our saiidi arms.
Let's start with the left hand down, right hand up, weight on the right foot, weight on the ball of the left foot, knees bent and lift the hip up and down and switch.
Up and down.
Now make sure when you lift that hip that you're not making the hand go up and down as well.
Your hip is moving in contrast to the hand and step and lift.
Step and lift.
Step.
Lift.
A little faster.
Step.
Lift.
Slow it down again and step.
Lift so you want your hands in place by the time your hip travels.
Step and lift and your chest always stays forward.
Good.
Knees point in the same direction.
Lift.
Step and lift.
Make sure both knees are bent so you don't get this up and down trying to get the hip moving.
Lift and step and lift.
Double time.
Step.
Lift.
Good.
Practice in front of a mirror make sure you're not bobbing up and down.
Make sure your hands aren't doing something funny.
You want nice clear lines.
Excellent.